A Guide to the University of Virginia Miller Fund Records: Miller School of Biology and Agriculture
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #10402
University of Virginia Miller Fund Records: Miller School of Biology and Agriculture 1869-1928
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
10402
ca. 400 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Deposit 1980 September 11
Container List
- Miller Fund Board Correspondence: R.T.W. Duke, Jr., Secretary/Treasurer, including a letter from E.A. Alderman, 1884-1927; (3 folders) (Box Box 1)
- Miller Fund Board: Insurance Policies, 1891-1893 (Box Box 1)
- Miller Fund Board: Original Deed with Samuel Miller and other documents, 1869-1877, 1882 (Box Box 1)
- Miller Fund Board: Reports, Statements, & Minutes, 1869-1870, 1883-1918, n.d. (Box Box 1)
- Miller Fund Board: University of Virginia Cabinet of Natural History Bonds, 1877 (Box Box 1)
- Miller Fund Board: Financial Records, 1881-1928; (4 folders) (Box Box 2)
- Miller Fund Board: Financial Records - Checks & Bankbooks, 1884-1924 (Box Box 2)
- Items pulled from Journals and Record Book (see bound volumes), 1878-1910, 1925, n.d. (Box Box 2)
- Record Book - Miller Fund Board of Trustees, 1869-1909 (Box Bound Volume)
- Journal - Miller Trust Fund of the University of Virginia, 1869-1926; (2 volumes) (Box Bound Volume)